http://www.artsandcraftstile.com/shipping-returns-privacy/

Schlabaugh Handmade Craftsman Mantel Clocks
Gift Items - Ready to Ship!
About Our Products
About Schlabaugh & Sons Clocks/Lamps About Motawi Tile About Tile Frames by Dard HunterAbout One Acre CeramicsAbout Porteous Tile
Arts & Crafts Period
Modern Arts & Crafts Style Ceramics, Pottery, & Tile MakersArts and Crafts StyleArt Nouveau Movement The Craftsman styleErnest A. BatchelderAbout Talwin Morris Mission StyleAbout Grueby Faience
Shipping, Returns & Privacy
About Us
Our Blog
Account Navigation
Account Navigation
My Account
Currency - All prices are in AUD
Currency - All prices are in AUD
Change Currency
Loading... Please wait...
Call us on 1-740-779-3300
My Account
Gift Certificates
Sign in or Create an account
Search
Contact Us
About Our Artists
Schlabaugh & SonsDard HunterYoshiko Yamamoto
About Our Products
About Schlabaugh & Sons Clocks/Lamps About Motawi Tile About Tile Frames by Dard HunterAbout One Acre CeramicsAbout Porteous Tile
Arts & Crafts Period
Modern Arts & Crafts Style Ceramics, Pottery, & Tile MakersArts and Crafts StyleArt Nouveau Movement The Craftsman styleErnest A. BatchelderAbout Talwin Morris Mission StyleAbout Grueby Faience
Shipping, Returns & Privacy
About Us
Our Blog
Search
Our Galleries
Our Galleries
Schlabaugh & Sons Clocks
Schlabaugh & Sons Craftsman Tile Clocks
Schlabaugh & Sons Craftsman Tile Lamps
Schlabaugh Handmade Craftsman Mantel Clocks
Gift Items - Ready to Ship!
Yoshiko Yamamoto Tile
Dard Hunter Fine China
Dard Hunter Frames
Decorative Home Goods
Brands
Brands
Dard Hunter StudiosSchlabaugh & SonsMotawi Tileworks
View all brands
HomeShipping, Returns & Privacy
Shipping, Returns & Privacy
Returns PolicyYou may return most items within 30 days of delivery for a refund. Customers are required to pay the return shipping costs and item must arrive at our warehouse in saleable condition. We encourage you to send your return appropriately packaged via Insured UPS and Prepaid.
Arts and Crafts Tile. com will pay the return shipping costs if the return is a result of our error (you received an incorrect, broken or defective item, etc.). We will accept order cancellations on stock items ordered which have not yet shipped from our warehouse. Orders for Custom made items may be cancelled within 24 hours of ordering without penalty. You should expect to receive your refund within four weeks of giving your package to the return shipper, however, in many cases you will receive a refund more quickly.
If you need to return an item or have any questions or problems with your order please contact us with the details at info@artsandcraftstile.com or call us at: 949-292-5682.  We pride ourselves on great customer service.
Installed tile:
We have no control over and are not responsible for the materials or method used to install the tile,  the skill of the installer, the type of maintenance, usage or amount of traffic. We do not therefore, guarantee the tile against chipping, cracking, spalling, discoloring, wearing, or scratching once it has been installed. We assume no obligation beyond the purchase price of products supplied by ArtsandCraftsTile.com and assume no liability for damages of any kind.
Shipping
We can ship to virtually any address in the world. Note that there are restrictions on some products, and some products cannot be shipped to international destinations. The web site shopping cart is set up for USA orders only. Please call or e-mail with questions or requests for International shipments and we will help you the best we can.Many items are in stock and ship right away. Other items are hand-crafted to order and take 4-6 weeks for shipping and delivery. Please let us know if you are in a rush for your items and we will do our best to accomodate. Express shipping options are also available.Please also note that the shipping rates for many items we sell are weight-based. The weight of any such item can be found on its detail page. To reflect the policies of the shipping companies we use, all weights will be rounded up to the next full pound.
Privacy Notice
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for Arts and Crafts Tile.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Newsletter signup
Name
Email
Further info
Contact Us
About Our Artists
Schlabaugh & SonsDard HunterYoshiko Yamamoto
About Our Products
About Schlabaugh & Sons Clocks/Lamps About Motawi Tile About Tile Frames by Dard HunterAbout One Acre CeramicsAbout Porteous Tile
Arts & Crafts Period
Modern Arts & Crafts Style Ceramics, Pottery, & Tile MakersArts and Crafts StyleArt Nouveau Movement The Craftsman styleErnest A. BatchelderAbout Talwin Morris Mission StyleAbout Grueby Faience
Shipping, Returns & Privacy
About Us
Our Blog
Our Galleries
Schlabaugh & Sons Clocks
Schlabaugh & Sons Craftsman Tile Clocks
Schlabaugh & Sons Craftsman Tile Lamps
Schlabaugh Handmade Craftsman Mantel Clocks
Gift Items - Ready to Ship!
Yoshiko Yamamoto Tile
Dard Hunter Fine China
Dard Hunter Frames
Decorative Home Goods
Brands
Dard Hunter StudiosSchlabaugh & SonsMotawi Tileworks
View all brands
Connect with us
Facebook
Pinterest
All prices are in USD. © 2020 ArtsAndCraftsTile.com | Sitemap
|
Powered by BigCommerce|Welcome to our Arts and Crafts Style Gallery! You will find Motawi Tile , The finest wood frames by Dard Hunter and craftsman clocks made by Schlabaugh and Sons. Motawi Tiles, Dard Hunter Frames and Schlabaugh & Sons Clocks will add beauty to your home and warmth to your heart. Handmade in the USA,
In stock and are ready to ship fully insured.
